<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quotes on Gert Van Gool</title>
    <link>http://gertvangool.be/tags/quotes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quotes on Gert Van Gool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 23:35:46 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://gertvangool.be/tags/quotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gertvangool.be/quote/classic-beautiful-traditional-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 23:35:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gertvangool.be/quote/classic-beautiful-traditional-products/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I find that young people want what their grandfathers had, not what their
fathers had. They want classic, beautiful, traditional products that they’re
going to keep forever. That’s the beauty of right now. They want to make a
smart purchase, and they’re willing to spend the money on something that they
like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;mdash; Frank Clegg in &lt;a href=&#34;http://pi.co/frank-clegg-leather-goods-maker/&#34;&gt;http://pi.co/frank-clegg-leather-goods-maker/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gertvangool.be/quote/things-that-have-never-been-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 17:22:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gertvangool.be/quote/things-that-have-never-been-done/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Do things that have never been done. &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Russell_A._Kirsch&#34;&gt;Russell
Kirsch&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&#34;http://joelrunyon.com/two3/an-unexpected-ass-kicking/&#34;&gt;An
Unexpected Ass Kicking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gertvangool.be/quote/simple-is-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 10:21:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gertvangool.be/quote/simple-is-hard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Simple is hard. #design &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/keeg/status/35126429528100864&#34;&gt;Keegan
Jones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Be Alone</title>
      <link>http://gertvangool.be/quote/how-to-be-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 21:25:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gertvangool.be/quote/how-to-be-alone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are at first lonely, be patient. If you&amp;rsquo;ve not been alone much, or if
when you were, you weren&amp;rsquo;t okay with it, then just wait. You&amp;rsquo;ll find it&amp;rsquo;s fine
to be alone once you&amp;rsquo;re embracing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could start with the acceptable places, the bathroom, the coffee shop, the
library. Where you can stall and read the paper, where you can get your
caffeine fix and sit and stay there. Where you can browse the stacks and smell
the books. You&amp;rsquo;re not supposed to talk much anyway so it&amp;rsquo;s safe there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s also the gym. If you&amp;rsquo;re shy you could hang out with yourself in
mirrors, you could put headphones in (guitar stroke).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And there&amp;rsquo;s public transportation, because we all gotta go places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And there&amp;rsquo;s prayer and meditation. No one will think less if you&amp;rsquo;re hanging
with your breath seeking peace and salvation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start simple. Things you may have previously (electric guitar plucking) based
on your avoid being alone principals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lunch counter. Where you will be surrounded by chow-downers. Employees who
only have an hour and their spouses work across town and so they &amp;ndash; like you
&amp;ndash; will be alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resist the urge to hang out with your cell phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you are comfortable with eat lunch and run, take yourself out for dinner.
A restaurant with linen and silverware. You&amp;rsquo;re no less intriguing a person
when you&amp;rsquo;re eating solo dessert to cleaning the whipped cream from the dish
with your finger. In fact some people at full tables will wish they were where
you were.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to the movies. Where it is dark and soothing. Alone in your seat amidst a
fleeting community.
And then, take yourself out dancing to a club where no one knows you. Stand on
the outside of the floor till the lights convince you more and more and the
music shows you. Dance like no one&amp;rsquo;s watching&amp;hellip;because, they&amp;rsquo;re probably not.
And, if they are, assume it is with best of human intentions. The way bodies
move genuinely to beats is, after all, gorgeous and affecting. Dance until
you&amp;rsquo;re sweating, and beads of perspiration remind you of life&amp;rsquo;s best things,
down your back like a brook of blessings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to the woods alone, and the trees and squirrels will watch for you.
Go to an unfamiliar city, roam the streets, there&amp;rsquo;re always statues to talk to
and benches made for sitting give strangers a shared existence if only for a
minute and these moments can be so uplifting and the conversations you get in
by sitting alone on benches might&amp;rsquo;ve never happened had you not been there by
yourself&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Society is afraid of alonedom, like lonely hearts are wasting away in
basements, like people must have problems if, after a while, nobody is dating
them. but lonely is a freedom that breaths easy and weightless and lonely is
healing if you make it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could stand, swathed by groups and mobs or hold hands with your partner,
look both further and farther for the endless quest for company. But no one&amp;rsquo;s
in your head and by the time you translate your thoughts, some essence of them
may be lost or perhaps it is just kept.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps in the interest of loving oneself, perhaps all those sappy slogans
from preschool over to high school&amp;rsquo;s groaning were tokens for holding the
lonely at bay. Cuz if you&amp;rsquo;re happy in your head than solitude is blessed and
alone is okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s okay if no one believes like you. All experience is unique, no one has
the same synapses, can&amp;rsquo;t think like you, for this be releived, keeps things
interesting lifes magic things in reach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you&amp;rsquo;re not connected, that communitie&amp;rsquo;s not present, just
take the perspective you get from being one person in one head and feel the
effects of it. take silence and respect it. if you have an art that needs a
practice, stop neglecting it. if your family doesn&amp;rsquo;t get you, or religious
sect is not meant for you, don&amp;rsquo;t obsess about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you could be in an instant surrounded if you needed it&lt;br/&gt;
If your heart is bleeding make the best of it &lt;br/&gt;
There is heat in freezing, be a testament.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k7X7sZzSXYs&#34;&gt;Tanya Davis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The road not taken</title>
      <link>http://gertvangool.be/quote/the-road-not-taken/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 08:21:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gertvangool.be/quote/the-road-not-taken/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two roads diverged in a yellow wood,&lt;br&gt;
And sorry I could not travel both&lt;br&gt;
And be one traveler, long I stood&lt;br&gt;
And looked down one as far as I could&lt;br&gt;
To where it bent in the undergrowth;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then took the other, as just as fair&lt;br&gt;
And having perhaps the better claim,&lt;br&gt;
Because it was grassy and wanted wear;&lt;br&gt;
Though as for that, the passing there&lt;br&gt;
Had worn them really about the same,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And both that morning equally lay&lt;br&gt;
In leaves no step had trodden black&lt;br&gt;
Oh, I kept the first for another day!&lt;br&gt;
Yet knowing how way leads on to way,&lt;br&gt;
I doubted if I should ever come back.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I shall be telling this with a sigh&lt;br&gt;
Somewhere ages and ages hence:&lt;br&gt;
two roads diverged in a wood, and I —&lt;br&gt;
I took the one less traveled by,&lt;br&gt;
And that has made all the difference.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;mdash; Robert Frost via &lt;a href=&#34;http://everythingannoys.me/post/200192370/the-road-not-taken-by-robert-frost&#34;&gt;Rob
Lofthouse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gertvangool.be/quote/only-the-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 13:20:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gertvangool.be/quote/only-the-best/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kun det bedste er godt nok &amp;mdash; Lego motto&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gertvangool.be/quote/build-prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 13:18:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gertvangool.be/quote/build-prototypes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You can build prototypes in the time it takes to have a meeting &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/simonw&#34;&gt;@simonw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gertvangool.be/quote/he-who-can-can/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 08:34:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gertvangool.be/quote/he-who-can-can/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://gertvangool.be/uploads/quote/he-who-can-can.png&#34; alt=&#34;He can who thinks he can, and he can&#39;t who thinks he can&#39;t. - Pablo
Picasso&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>